Finding Aid for Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies (University of Michigan) Records, 1892-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- University Units, 1952-2008
  - 1970-1991
    - Schools and Colleges
      - LSA, College of
        - Economics
          - Applied Economics
            - Program Proposal, 1974 (Box 130)
            - Review, 1980 (Box 130)
          - Site visit, 1987 (Box 130)
        - English Languages and Literatures
          - General, 1985-1991 (Box 130)
          - Conference on Narrative Theory, 1987 (Box 130)
          - Creative Writing Program (doctoral), 1989 (Box 130)
          - Site Visit, 1987 (Box 130)
        - Far East Languages and Literatures, 1985 (Box 130)
        - Geography, 1981-1989 (Box 130)
        - Geology
          - General, 1987-1990 (Box 130)
          - Site Visit, 1988 (Box 130)
        - German Languages and Literatures
          - General, 1986-1991 (Box 130)
          - Review, 1985 (Box 130)
        - History
          - General, 1986-1991; 2 folders (Box 130)
          - Departmental Review, 1971 (Box 130)
          - External Review, 1990 (Box 130)
          - Internal Review, 1990 (Box 130)
          - Post Emancipation Project, 1990 (Box 130)
          - Site Visit, 1987 (Box 130)
        - History of Art
          - General, 1986-1991 (Box 130)
          - Review, 1989 (Box 130)
          - Site Visit, 1990 (Box 130)
        - Journalism, 1986-1990 (Box 131)
        - Linguistics, 1986-1990 (Box 131)
        - Mathematics
          - General, 1986-1991 (Box 131)
          - Site Visits, 1986; 1990; 2 folders (Box 131)
        - Near Eastern Studies
          - General, 1977-1991 (Box 131)
          - Site Visit, 1986 (Box 131)
        - Philosophy
          - General, 1987-1990 (Box 131)
          - Site Visit, 1988 (Box 131)
        - Physics, 1985-1991 (Box 131)
        - Political Sciences
          - General, 1981-1991 (Box 131)
          - Site Visit, 1987 (Box 131)
        - Psychology
          - General, 1986-1991 (Box 131)
          - Site Visit, 1987 (Box 131)
        - Religion, Studies in, 1988 (Box 131)
        - Romance Languages and Literatures
          - General, 1986-1990 (Box 131)
          - Site Visit, 1989 (Box 131)
        - Slavic Languages and Literatures
          - General, 1986-1991 (Box 131)
          - Review, 1986 (Box 131)
        - Sociology
          - General, 1986-1991 (Box 131)
          - Review, 1989 (Box 131)
          - Site Visits, 1986; 1989; 2 folders (Box 131)
          - William Sewell, 1988-1990 (Box 131)
        - Statistics
          - General, 1990 (Box 131)
          - Statistics and Applied Statistics Site Visit, 1986 (Box 131)
          - Applied Statistics, 1985-1990 (Box 131)
          - Program Proposal, 1969-1989 (Box 131)
          - Review
            - 1976 (Box 131)
            - 1990 (Box 131)
        - Theater
          - General, 1986-1987 (Box 131)
          - Master's in Fine Arts (MFA), 1970-1990 (Box 131)
      - Medical School
        - General, 1985-1991 (Box 131)
        - Biological Chemistry, 1966-1990 (Box 131)
        - Curriculum, 1986-1987 (Box 131)
        - Dual Ph.D. / Pharm.D. Program, 1984 (Box 131)
        - Educational Liaison Committee Meeting, December, 1986 (Box 131)
        - Human Genetics, 1989-1990 (Box 131)
        - Medical Scientist Training Program (MSTP)
          - General, 1986-1991 (Box 131)
          - Policy Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 131)
        - Pathology, 1989 (Box 132)
        - Physical Medicine
          - General, 1986 (Box 132)
          - Rehabilitation Review, 1973 (Box 132)
        - Physiology Site Visit, 1989 (Box 132)
      - Music, School of
        - General, 1986-1991 (Box 132)
        - Computer Applications, 1971-1974 (Box 132)
        - Conducting DMA Program Development, 1977 (Box 132)
        - Faculty Meeting, 1989 (Box 132)
        - Graduate Programs, 1987-1991 (Box 132)
        - MFA in Dance Proposal, 1975 (Box 132)
        - Music Theory Graduate Proposal, c, 1970 (Box 132)
        - Music Theory Program, 1989-1990 (Box 132)
        - Site Visit, 1986 (Box 132)
      - Natural Resources, College of
        - General, 1985-1991 (Box 132)
        - Environmental Task Force (Dean Search), 1990-1991 (Box 132)
        - Landscape Architecture, 1984 (Box 132)
        - Master's in Science (MS), 1971-1989 (Box 132)
        - Review, 1985 (Box 132)
      - Nursing, School of
        - Accreditation Visit, Fall 1985 (Box 132)
        - Administration, 1985-1991; 2 folders (Box 132)
        - Anesthesia Training Program, 1986 (Box 132)
        - Community Health Nursing (MS), 1986-1987 (Box 132)
        - Gerontological Nursing (MS), 1986 (Box 132)
        - Health Services Administration, 1961-1975 (Box 132)
        - Medical / Surgical Nursing, 1986 (Box 132)
        - M.S. / M.B.A. Proposal, Undated (Box 132)
        - Ph.D. Proposal, 1974-1975 (Box 132)
        - Pharmacy, 1985-1990 (Box 132)
        - Physical Education, Division of, 1985-1987 (Box 132)
        - Psychiatric / Mental Health Nursing, 1960-1989 (Box 132)
        - Review
          - 1980 (Box 132)
          - M.S. and Ph.D. Programs, 1981; 2 folders (Box 132)
          - Response to Program Recommendations, 1983 (Box 132)
      - Public Health, School of
        - General, 1976-1991 (Box 133)
        - Biostatistics, 1973-1974 (Box 133)
        - Clinical Research, 1983 (Box 133)
        - Conference on AIDS, 1986 (Box 133)
        - Environmental and Industrial Health Review
          - 1973, 2 folders (Box 133)
          - 1976 (Box 133)
        - Epidemiology, Site Visit, 1989 (Box 133)
        - Pedontics / MPH in Dental Public Health, 1984 (Box 133)
        - Population Environment, 1988-1990 (Box 133)
        - Population Planning, 1976-1986 (Box 133)
        - Population Planning and International Health, 1986-1990 (Box 133)
        - Site Visit, 1986 (Box 133)
        - Toxicology, 1979-1988 (Box 133)
      - Social Work, School of
        - General, 1986-1989 (Box 133)
        - Social Psychology, 1970 (Box 133)
  - 1989-1996
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of, 1996 (Box 187)
    - Art, School of, 1990-1993 (Box 187)
    - Business, School of, 1991 (Box 187)
    - Dentistry, School of, 1989-1992 (Box 187)
    - Education, School of, 1989-1995 (Box 187)
    - Engineering, College of
      - General, 1992-1995 (Box 187)
      - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Dept. of, 1990 (Box 187)
    - Information and Library Studies, School of, 1990-1994 (Box 187)
    - Kinesiology, Division of, 1993 (Box 192)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
      - American Culture, 1996 (Box 187)
      - Asian Languages and Culture, 1993 (Box 187)
      - Biophysics Research, 1991-1992 (Box 192)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2067 ]
      - Chemistry, 1991-1996 (Box 187)
      - Chinese Studies, 1989 (Box 187)
      - Classical Art and Archaeology, Interdepartmental Program in (IPCAA), 1994-1996 (Box 187)
      - Economics, 1993-1995 (Box 187)
      - English Language and Literature, undated (Box 187)
      - English-Creative Writing, 1990-1994 (Box 192)
      - History, 1993-1995 (Box 192)
      - History of Art, 1990-1991 (Box 192)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2066 ]
      - Mathematics, 1991 (Box 187)
      - Physics, undated (Box 187)
      - Political Science, 1990-1995 (Box 192)
      - Psychology, 1991-1996 (Box 187)
      - Psychology-Clinical Psychology, 1991 (Box 187)
      - Public Policy Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 187)
      - Romance Languages and Literatures, 1994 (Box 187)
      - Sociology, 1993-1995 (Box 192)
    - Medicine, School of
      - General, 1989-1992 (Box 187)
      - Anatomy and Cell Biology, 1994 (Box 187)
      - Cellular and Molecular Biology, 1994 (Box 187)
      - Human Genetics, 1991 (Box 187)
      - Medical and Biological Illustration, 1990-1991 (Box 187)
      - Medical Scientist Training Program, 1990-1991 (Box 187)
      - Medicinal Chemistry, 1993 (Box 187)
      - Microbiology and Immunology, 1992 (Box 187)
      - Recruitment and Retention Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 187)
    - Music, School of, 1989-1996; 2 folders (Box 192)
    - Natural Resources, School of, 1991-1992 (Box 187)
    - Nursing, School of, 1991-1993 (Box 187)
    - Pharmacy, College of, 1989-1994 (Box 187)
    - Public Policy, School of, 1996 (Box 187)
    - Social Work, School of
      - Joint Program in Social Work and Social Science, 1989-1995; 2 folders (Box 187)
  - 1977-2009
    The bulk of the University Units, 1977-2009 subseries consists of materials relating to the Rackham Summer Interdisciplinary Institute (RSII). RSII was first held in 1998 and consisted of a five-week program with twenty faculty and ten graduate students completing readings and attending weekly sessions involving small group and general discussions on a wide range of topics in interdisciplinary studies, in particular how to support interdisciplinary scholarship and teaching. Materials include faculty and student application files as well as annual files containing correspondence, budget information, agendas and meeting notes, selection process information, and reports. Other units represented in this series include the Clements Library, engineering program, University of Michigan Museum of Art (UMMA), and the Psychological Clinic.
    - Rackham Summer Interdisciplinary Institute (RSII)
      - Faculty
        - General, 2002-2004; 2 folders (Box 230)
        - Balogh, Lajob, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Bertellini, Giorio, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Bornstein, George, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Campbell, Scott, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Cooper, Vaughn, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Dickie, Simon, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Ellis, Ronald, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Hofweber, Thomas, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Jones, Martha, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Kotre, John, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Kucich, John, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Mahalingam, Ram, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Matjias, Christian, 2002 (Box 230)
        - McKay, Timothy, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Misra, Dawn, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Nagata, Donna, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Norich, Anita, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Porter, David, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Rappe, Sara, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Schultz, William, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Stern, Jeffrey, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Sturman, Rachel, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Wilson, Jessica, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Wintraub, Michael, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Zak, Albin, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Zorn, Jens, 2002 (Box 230)
      - Graduate Students
        - Agrawal, Divya, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Alarcon, Saul, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Arvey, Sarah, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Behling, John, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Birk, Nancy, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Callahan, Mollie, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Caza, Arran, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Choudhary, Ruchi, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Corona, Xavier, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Daligga, Catherine, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Davidson, Roei, 2002 (Box 230)
        - DeFreece, Alfred, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Dietsch, Thomas, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Dinzey, Zaire, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Dubisson, Eva-Marie, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Duh, Geoffrey, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Duker, Philip, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Ejmont, Sylvia, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Erazo, Juliet, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Foelman, Katrina, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Ford, Kristie, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Gaynor, Jennifer, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Gocmen, Zeynep, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Gowda, Chandon, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Haman, Marcelo, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Haritatos, Jana, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Harrington, Matthew, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Howey, Meghan, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Ides, Matthew, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Jigoulov, Vadim, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Johnson, Karen, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Jokic, Olivera, 2002 (Box 230)
        - L'Heurevx Lewis, Ronald, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Lambepin, Frederique, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Lavicza, Zsolt, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Le Nay, Jerome, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Lee, Sangyum, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Lee, Wen-Yu, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Leichtnam, Christopher, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Lewis, Geoffrey, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Li, Sumiao, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Lieber, Jeffrey, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Lin, Brenda, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Lipchin, Clive, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Madhavan-Reese, Sneha, 2002 (Box 230)
        - McGrath, Stacy, 2002 (Box 230)
        - McManus, Stanton, 2002 (Box 230)
        - McNaughton, James, 2002 (Box 230)
        - McNeill, Darrick, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Min, Li, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Mudaliar, Nikhil, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Ng, Jonathan, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Pang, Joyce, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Pas, Justine, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Pedersen, David, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Peterson, Rachel, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Rama, Robert, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Ramirez, Pablo, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Ravishankar, Viswanathan, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Ross, Deanna, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Rudy, Bruce, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Ryan, Marianne, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Segar, Michelle, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Shah, Sudh, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Silva, Evandro, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Tamada, Vindhya, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Thiels, John, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Tirosh, Yofi, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Van Arsdale, Adam, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Vecchiola, Carla, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Wampuszyc, Eva, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Yoo, Mina, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Zhang, Yanyan, 2002 (Box 230)
        - Zhou, Lingling, 2002 (Box 230)
      - Interdisciplinary Seminars, 1998-1999 (Box 230)
      - Interdisciplinary Seminars, 1999-2000 (Box 230)
      - Interdisciplinary Seminars, 2000-2001 (Box 230)
      - Interdisciplinary Seminars, 2001-2002 (Box 231)
      - Interdisciplinary Seminars, 2002 (Box 231)
      - Interdisciplinary Seminars, 2005 (Box 231)
      - Postdocs
        - Fomin, Vladislavs, 2002 (Box 231)
        - O'Donnell, Thomas, 2002 (Box 231)
        - Saha, Robin, 2002 (Box 231)
      - Rackham Interdisciplinary Program, 1998 (Box 231)
      - Rackham Interdisciplinary Program, 2003-2004 (Box 231)
      - RSII, 1998 (Box 231)
      - RSII (photos included), 1999 (Box 231)
      - RSII, 2000 (Box 231)
      - RSII, 2001 (Box 232)
      - RSII Co-Directors Binder (photos included), 2001 (Box 232)
      - RSII Financial and Information Binder, 2000 (Box 232)
      - RSII Introductory Packet, 2000 (Box 232)
      - RSII Introductory Packet, 2002 (Box 232)
      - RSII Scale, Size, Measure, and Volume, 2002 (Box 232)
      - Summary Information, 1998-2001 (Box 232)
    - Other Units
      - Clements Library, 1991-1993 (Box 196)
      - Engineering Program Files
        - Ann Arbor Correspondence, 1991-1996; 2 folders (Box 195)
        - Dearborn Engineering Files Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 195)
        - Dearborn Master of Public Administration Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 195)
        - Dearborn Program Files, 1991-1995; 2 folders (Box 195)
      - Institute for Human Adjustment, 1987-1993; 2 folders (Box 196)
      - Museum of Art, 1990-1993; 2 folders (Box 196)
      - Osborn Preserve, 1977 (Box 196)
      - Psychological Clinic, 1987-1993 (Box 196)
      - Reading and Learning Skills Center, 1988-1993 (Box 196)
      - University Center for the Child and the Family, 1987-1994 (Box 196)
      - Wallenberg Committee and Lectures, 1990-2000
        - Biophysics Research Division, 1996 (Box 196)
        - Classical Art and Archaeology, 1996 (Box 196)
        - Economics, 1994 (Box 196)
        - English Language and Literature, 1992 (Box 196)
        - English Language Institute, 1999 (Box 196)
        - History Department, 2000 (Box 196)
        - Linguistics, 1999 (Box 226)
        - Mathematics, 1992 (Box 226)
        - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 2002 (Box 226)
        - Philosophy, 1991; 2001; 2 folders (Box 226)
        - Psychology, 1997 (Box 226)
        - Rackham Administrative, 1996 (Box 226)
        - Romance Languages and Literatures, 1995 (Box 226)
        - Sociology, 1997 (Box 226)
        - Statistics, 2001 (Box 226)
      - Financial Engineering Program Review, 2007 (Box 226)
      - Geological Science Program Review, 2007 (Box 226)
      - GE: Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (UROP), 2000 (Box 209)
      - Graduate Program Information, 2008-2009 (Box 209)
      - Graduate Program Reviews, 2006 (Box 226)
      - Industrial and Operations Engineering Program Review, 2007 (Box 226)
      - Internal Reviews
        - Automotive Systems Engineering, 2002 (Box 226)
        - Art, History of, 1998 (Box 226)
        - Culture and Cognition, 1999 (Box 226)
        - Music, 1995 (Box 226)
        - Nuclear Engineering and Radiological Sciences, 2000 (Box 227)
        - Nursing, 2001; 2 folders (Box 227)
      - Macromolecular Science and Engineering Review, 2006 (Box 227)
      - Masters of Science in Software Engineering Report, 2005 (Box 227)
      - Materials Science and Engineering Program Review, 2007 (Box 227)
      - Mathematics Review, 2006 (Box 227)
      - McNair Program, 1998-2009; 3 folders (Box 209)
      - Mechanical Engineering Review, 2006; 2009 (Box 227)
      - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering External Review, 2002 (Box 227)
      - National Name Exchange Program, 2001 (Box 209)
      - Nuclear Engineering and Radiological Sciences Program Review, 2007 (Box 227)
      - Overall Program Review Survey Results, 2006 (Box 227)
      - Program Reviews, 2006-2008; 2 folders (Box 227)
      - Project Approval Form (PAF), 2005 (Box 209)
      - Rackham Campaign Report and Resources, 2004 (Box 227)
      - Rackham Data and Korean Studies Program, 1996-2007 (Box 209)
      - SGUS Program, 2004 (Box 209)
      - Spring/Summer Research Review, 2001 (Box 227)
      - Statistics and Applied Statistics Program Review, 2007 (Box 227)
      - Statistics Program External Review, 2001 (Box 227)
      - Summer Research Opportunity Program/Emerge, 2000 (Box 209)
      - Summer Research Opportunity Program, 2004 (Box 209)
      - Summer Research Opportunity/Summer Institute, 2006 (Box 209)
      - Task Force on Testing and Training Prospective GSIs Report, 2002 (Box 227)
      - WISE Program, 2000 (Box 209)
- Program Evaluation Office, 1972-2007
  The Program Evaluation Office series consists of the files of Carole Berlin, the former Rackham administrator responsible for the Program Evaluation Office within the Rackham Graduate School. The series is divided into two subseries: Program Evaluations and Administrative files.
  - Program Evaluations, 1978-1992
    The Program Evaluation series (11.5 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically by department or program. The records, spanning 1978-1992, principally contain material relating to the periodic evaluations of the various departments and interdepartmental programs administered by Rackham. The evaluations are performed to analyze both successful and unsuccessful features of the programs. There is information on the entire evaluation process, from the organization of the review committee to the preparation of the committee's final report. The report contains a brief history of the department or program, a discussion of its nature and costs, and recommendations for improvements. Other material in the series includes memos concerning the implementation of changes proposed by the review committees; statistical data about enrollment; and student, faculty, and alumni questionnaires, which assess the success of programs.
    The digital files in the Program Evaluation series are functionally related to earlier content collected and maintained by Carole Berlin, the former Rackham administrator responsible for the Program Evaluation Office within the Rackham Graduate School. The digital materials in this series include evaluations of graduate programs at U-M Dearborn and U-M Flint as well as at the main Ann Arbor campus. Documents are scanned versions of original paper records.
    - Albion College (joint AB/MPP), 1982 (Box 95)
    - American Culture Program, 1976-1992
      - Dean's List (Box 95)
      - Flint (Box 95)
      - Review Committee, 2 folders (Box 95)
    - Anatomy and Cell Biology Program, 1984 (Box 95)
    - Ancient History Interdepartmental Program, 1990 (Box 95)
    - Anesthesia/Flint Masters of Science, 1991 (Box 95)
    - Anthropology Program, 1989 (Box 95)
    - Anthropology-History, 1987-1991 (Box 95)
    - Applied Economics Masters Review, 1980-1990 (Box 95)
    - Applied Linguistics Program, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Applied Physics (new graduate program), 1986 (Box 95)
    - Applied Social Research or Sociology Program, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Applied Statistics Program, 1986-1990 (Box 95)
    - Architecture Program, 1982-1989
      - General, 8 folders (Box 95)
      - Professional Master's Accreditation (Box 95)
      - Student and Faculty Questionnaires (Box 95)
      - Vienna American School of Architecture (Box 95)
    - Art (M.F.A. and M.A.), 1989 (Box 95)
    - Asian Language and Cultures Department, 1987-1991
      - General (Box 96)
      - Buddhist Studies, 1982-1986 (Box 96)
    - Asian Studies Program, 1984-1991 (Box 96)
    - Asian Studies: Japan and China and Journalism Masters, 1991 (Box 96)
    - Astronomy Department, 1988-1990 (Box 96)
    - Biochemistry, 1989-1990 (Box 96)
    - Bioengineering Program, 1978-1991; 4 folders (Box 96)
    - Bioengineering/Biomaterials Interdepartmental Degree Program, 1991 (Box 96)
    - Biological Sciences Department, 1990-1991 (Box 96)
    - Biology Department Self-Study, 1990 (Box 96)
    - Biomedical Research Council, 1991 (Box 96)
    - Biophysics Program, 1985-1992; 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Biotechnology Grant Application, 1989; 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Bush Program in Child Development and Social Policy, 1983 (Box 96)
    - Business Administration, School of, 1991-1992 (Box 96)
    - Cellular and Molecular Biology Program, 1984; 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Certificate of Graduate Studies, 1978-79 (Box 97)
    - Chemistry, 1989-1991; 1 folders; 1 volumes (Box 97)
    - Child and the Family, Center for, 1986-1992
      - General, 2 folders (Box 97)
      - Budget (Box 97)
      - Directorship (Box 97)
      - Transition Committee (Box 97)
    - Children's Center, 1979-1992; 2 folders (Box 97)
    - Child Care Center Law School Proposal, 1990 (Box 97)
    - Chinese Studies, 1989 (Box 97)
    - Civil and Environmental Engineering Department, 1990 (Box 97)
    - Classical Art and Archaeology Program, 1984 (Box 97)
    - Classical Studies, 1991 (Box 97)
    - Clements Library, 1992 (Box 97)
    - Clinical Research Design and Statistical Analysis, 1983-1991 (Box 97)
    - Cognitive Science Program, 1991 (Box 97)
    - Communications Program, 1989-1992 (Box 97)
    - Community Health Nursing Program, 1987-1991 (Box 97)
    - Comparative Literature Program, 1977-1992; 2 folders (Box 97)
    - Computer Aided Design Masters, 1982 (Box 97)
    - Computer and Communication Sciences Program, 1983 (Box 97)
    - Computer Information and Control Engineering, 1977-1983; 2 folders (Box 97)
    - Construction Engineering and Movement and Masters of Business Administration Dual Degree Program, 1987-1988 (Box 97)
    - Creative Writing, Masters of Fine Arts, 1982-1985 (Box 97)
    - Dearborn Campus, Graduate Programs, 1991-1992 (Box 97)
    - Dentist/Scientist Award Program, 1988 (Box 97)
    - Dentistry, School of, 1990-1992 (Box 98)
    - Development Neurobiology Training Grant, 1990 (Box 98)
    - Economics Department, 1979-1983 (Box 98)
    - Education, School of, 1967-1988
      - General, 2 folders (Box 98)
      - Combined Degrees (Box 98)
      - Continuing Professional Development (Box 98)
      - Correspondence (Box 98)
      - MA Dearborn Campus (Box 98)